

1991/11/09

Male

**** 097 812 9429

✓ darkcompet@gmail.com

🔠 Ho Chi Minh city

DESCRIPTION

I am a software engineer who has worked on a number kinds of small and big OOP-based projects for 5 years. I am interested in Mathematics, Data-structure & Algorithm, and got high-ranked on some online programming contest sites like hackerrank, atcoder... I like coding and hope to find a job which has new challenges in every day.

SKILLS

Bash, C/C++, C#, Unit

80%

ava, Kotlin, Android, PH

90%

Javascript, Nodejs, SQLite, MySQL

Spring Boot, Flutte

50%

HTML, CSS

INTERESTS

- Chess, Pingpong, Volleyball
- Traditional film and musi

EDUCATION

QUANG XUONG 2 HIGHSCHOOL 2006/09 - 2009/06

Natural Science course

(Math, Physics, Chemistry...)

HANOI UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY 2009/09 - 2011/03

Electronic Engineering and Communication course

(Basic Math, Physics, C/C++...)

TOKYO JAPANESE LANGUAGE EDUCATION CENTER 2011/04 - 2012/03

Jananese course

(Math, Physics, Chemistry, Japanese, English...)

NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, AKASHI COLLEGE 2012/04 - 2015/03

Electrical and Computer Engineering course

(Electrical circuit, Datastructure & Algorithm, Graph theory...)

THE UNIVERSITY OF ELECTRO-COMMUNICATIONS, TOKYO 2015/04 - 2017/03

Computer Science course

(Datastructure & Algorithm, Game theory, Graph theory...)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android Developer at www.leontec.co.ip

- **2015/10 2017/12**
- · Develop Android barcode-based apps.
- · Skill: Debugging, Multi-threading, RESTful Api.

Android Developer at www.fujinet.net

- **2018/04 2018/07**
- · Android skill: Custom Views, Design Pattern,...
- · Server skill: Google Cloud Platform server config (Compute engine, BigQuery, Dataflow...), Springboot api development.

IT Comtor at https://posapp.vn/en/

2018/08 - 2019/08

Directly get requirements from JCustomer and schedule/breakdown them for VTeam.

- · Touching site: https://go-eki.com/.
- · PHP skill: Pure php implementation.

Android, C# Developer at https://tgl-sol.com/

- **2019/09 2020/03**
- · Android app development: Path Finding (ARCore), Wall Detection (OpenCV), Air-conditioner remote control (IoT).
- · Windows PC-app maintenance.
- · Framework: Android java, .NET, Arduino C++.

Bridge engineer at https://marble-d.co.jp/

2020/04 - 2021/12

Acts as TaskHandler between JCustomer and VTeam. Also work as a developer, website maintainer.

- Touching sites: https://sommelier.jp/, https://fit.nikkin.co.jp/, https://c-hotline.net/,...
- · Frameworks: Cakephp, Codeigniter, Laravel.
- · Services: Google Analytics, Spiral, Robot Payment,...

Unity C# game developer

2021/12 - now

For now still in developing a multiplayer game.

- · Client skill: oauth with 3rd-provider, async/await with Task/UniTask, coroutine, scene layout, asset bundle loading.
- · Server skill: RESTful api (PHP, C# or Kotlin...). Realtime with magiconion.

CERTIFICATIONS

· N2 at Japanese Language Proficiency Test

July, 2013

- TOEIC 600 at Proficiency Public Test
 - Public Test July, 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

List of my app publishing in App Store:

 $\cdot \ \mathsf{Gps} \ \mathsf{Compass: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=compet.gpscompass}$